websparrow.org 2019-11-04

# Privacy Policy - Websparrow

December 28, 2017 | Updated: July 15, 2018 

* * *

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site [websparrow.org](https://www.websparrow.org/). This Privacy Policy is meant to help you understand what data we collect, why we collect it, and what we do with it. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

* * *

### Information we collect

We collect information to provide better services to all of our users like.

**Email id:**  To create the e-card we use email id to identify the user uniquely and sent their card details on the email. Besides creating e-card, we do not ask for user email id anywhere else in our website.

**Cookies and similar technologies:**  A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user computer tied to information about the user, browser or device. Our site uses cookies only for session validation.

**Log information:**  Like most standard website servers, we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and the number of clicks to analyse trends, administer the site, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### How we use the information we collect?

We use the information we collect from all of our services to provide, maintain, protect and improve them, to develop new ones, and to protect users. We also use this information to offer you optimized contents. We use information collected from cookies and other technologies, to improve your user experience, the overall quality of our services and validation of user. Your email id defines you as a unique user over all the website.

### External links

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

### Changes to this Privacy Statements

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy  of WebSparrow.org then you may contact me through the [contact us](https://www.websparrow.org/contact-us) page.

Best Regards,

The Websparrow Team
